# Dan Akimoto

## Blockchain Full-Stack Developer

Quebec, Canada

@ danakimoto319@gmail.com

A https://github.com/crazydream000

## **SUMMARY**

Highly 7+ years experienced senior blockchain full stack developer with a focus on contract development using Solidity and Rust. My expertise extends to backend development with Python and Node.js, as well as frontend development using React and Vue. Also have a strong background in project management and software testing where you excel in designing and implementing comprehensive test plans to ensure the reliability and stability of your software, so successfully leading and delivering complex blockchain projects.

#### **EDUCATION**



### California Baptist University

**5** 09 / 2013 – 08 / 2017

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

#### **EXPERIENCE**



Blockchain Fullstack developer

06 / 2023 ~ 04 / 2024

- Served as blockchain full stack developer for the Landshare project, rwa platform built on Binance Smart Chain.
- Spearheaded the implementation of the platform's landing page using webflow, focusing on creating
  an engaging and visually appealing user interface that effectively communicated the platform's value
  proposition implemented others using React/Next Framework.
- Leveraged the React/Next.js framework to develop and deployed various contracts across the platform, including the Staking vault, NFT game, Swap, and DAO functionalities.
- Helped to launch the landshare v2 on binance smart chain, but also plume network.
- Managed a blockchain project using agile methodologies and Jira as the project management tool.



02 / 2022 ~ 06 / 2023

- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to design and implement decentralized financial applications for asset management, trading, and lending.
- Buit various Bots like Keeper, OpenBook Crank, Settler, Liquidator to keep exchange operating system on Mango project.
- Developed Solana programs with Rust for swap, borrow, voting features
- Demonstrated a strong understanding of scalability, security, and performance considerations when developing blockchain applications.
- Coordinated the development team, set project milestones, and ensured timely delivery of highquality software.
- Participate in code reviews and provide feedback to improve overall project quality.
- Analyzed 30+ user requirements to derive technical software design and performance requirements.



Lead Developer

04 / 2021 ~ 06/ 2022

- Designed and programmed a supply chain management system utilizing blockchain technology, resulting in a 50% reduction in tracking errors.
- Developed decentralized applications such as NFT marketplaces, crowdfunding platforms, and decentralized exchanges, attracting over 2,500 daily active users cumulatively.
- Integrated prominent DeFi protocols like Uniswap, Compound, and Aave with decentralized applications, allowing seamless access to financial services for over 3,000 users.
- Constructed smart contracts on Ethereum and Binance Smart Chain blockchains using Solidity programming language, providing secure execution of business logic for 5 different enterprise clients.
- Implemented end-to-end ERP Blockchain API solutions for SyncFab customers using blockchain and other SyncFab services using Golang, Gorilla Mux and Go-Web3.



ChainGPT

Software Engineer

09 / 2020 ~ 04/ 2021

- Led a team of 3 developers working on smart contract development.
- Developed Vote contracts for DAO system.
- Participated in frontend development of dashboard of site.
- Introduced new development practices including version control using Git and peer code review.



09 / 2017 - 03 / 2020

- Developed and maintained enterprise-grade blockchain solutions using Rust and Ethereum Smart
   Contracts
- Actively participated in the full software development lifecycle, from requirements gathering to design, implementation, testing, deployment, and maintenance.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to design and implement decentralized financial (DeFi)
   applications for asset management, trading, and lending
- Contributed to open-source Rust projects and participated in Rust community events
- Worked with clients to understand their business needs and provided solutions that aligned with their strategic objectives
- Built and maintained production-ready smart contracts on Ethereum platform



#### Senior Frontend Developer

2 / 2017 - 9 / 2017

- Worked on creating a responsive website for smart devices using responsive design and media queries.
- Utilized various JavaScript and jQuery libraries, AJAX for form validation and other interactive features.
- Responsible for authoring of website functionality with JavaScript, HTML, CSS.
- Design and developed the responsive web application using Web3, Angular2, NodeJs, Ajax,
   JavaScript JQuery, Css, Developer Tool technologies.
- Implemented a common styling with the help of CSS across entire application that controls color, layout, width, height, font size, images size and accomplished other graphic related features.
- Lead a team of developers to deliver projects on time and within budget

8 / 2016 - 2 / 2017

- Mastered PHP Framework : Laravel, by working with 25 + projects.
- Designed and oversaw wireframe designs of over 30 web & mobile apps from client requests.
- Created accessible, responsive and functional user interfaces to allow visitors on any device to have the same perfect user experience.
- Worked with clients to understand product positioning to incorporate into ad copy, leading to client satisfaction of 96%.

## **Tech Skills**

Blockchain Architecture	Cryptography	DAPP	Team Leadership
Next.js	Solidity	Rust	Ruby on Rails
Vue	DJango	Python	NodeJS

# Most proud of

## Critical Thinking

Consider myself one of the people who use System 2 of the brain: rational and evidence-based decision maker.

## → Fast Learner

I'm really fond of learning and try to develop the project with new language so that the clients could be satisfied.

## **iii** Good Communicator & Team Player

Excellent communicator and team player, which helps me to collaborate effectively with others